this problem has given us
a local variable colors referencing an
array of strings
representing four different colors
we've been asked to use the array each
method
to iterate over colors and print each
element
iterating over arrays is a common task
and the array each method is very useful
for this
we call the each method on our
collection which is colors in this case
and we're going to pass a block to this
method invocation
we create that block using do end
we need to name a block parameter
which will be a variable local to this
block
as each iterates through our array each
element of the array will be passed to
the block
and assigned to the block parameter
which we've named
color for each element of the array
that's passed to the block we want to
perform
some task and in this case that's
outputting the color
so we can invoke put s
and we'll output a string using string
interpolation
to output the string referenced by our
block parameter
color
let's run our code
and we've gotten the expected output